MENACHEM MENDEL HOFFMAN

Address: Sydney, Australia • Mobile: 0401717940

Email: mendelhoffman2015@gmail.com • LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/menachemhoffman

CAREER PROFILE

Currently studying computer science with an initial aspiration of becoming become a full stack developer within next the five years. In time, inspire to be a to become a junior backend developer with a particular interest in data science, solving complex problems for people and a strong track record of working with large teams to complete deliverables for programing development

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science

Deakin University, Melbourne, Australia

March 2021 - Present

- Learning a range of subject with computer language such as C# with Object-Oriented programming
- Python with the data structures course

Diploma of Applied Information Technology

Latrobe University, Melbourne, Australia

September 2019 - January 2021

- Received a sound background of computer hardware, computer software and Internet of things devices
- Object-Oriented programming in Java

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Proficient Object-Oriented programing in Java and C#
- Informed Relational Databases with AWS in SQL
- Skilled in Web development with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, framework Vue.js
- Competent with Data Structures in Python

EXPERIENCE

The Kashrut Authority, Sydney, Australia

November 2019 - Present

Field Supervisor

· Managed clients to ensure their food is up to kosher highest standards for the local community

Kesser Torah College, Sydney, Australia

January 2014 - September 2016

Assistant Network Manager

- Played a role in the school's local area network management team, including the maintenance and troubleshooting of the 100-plus network of personal computers and iPads
- Provided technical assistance with audio-visual presentations at annual school events, including assemblies and speech nights

PROFESSIONAL MEMBERSHIPS

Australian Computer Society ASC, Associate Member

March 2021 - Present

Membership Number :4288514

- The society provides a variety of services to enable students to increase technical knowledge and capability in computer science including hackathons and local area meetups
- Assists with finding student's internships and graduate positions
- The professional society facilitates networking opportunities and training with other data science professionals
- Provides the environment to explore the opportunities in software development space and data science

REFEREES

• Reference available upon request